Who here does not have a reliable way of getting customers?
As in like you get it all word of mouth predominantly.
Okay, one of the biggest mistakes that you make
from an acquisition perspective
is using a warm process on cold leads.
The reverse always works and the inverse does not.
Meaning, if you use a warm process on cold leads,
you will not sell people and you will only sell
the six inch putts, which are the warm leads.
Which you pretty much could just be like,
here's the price, buy it.
On the other hand, if you have a cold acquisition process,
you can put a warm lead through it
and they will buy at higher rates.
Who here was at the launch for the book?
At the launch, many people who were there knew who I was.
There were also people there who did not know who I was.
The webinar was structured for people
who had no idea who I was.
The people who did know were not offended.
The people who didn't know were grateful to find out.
I could have probably sent an email with the offer
and done a third of the sales we did.
The other two thirds came from actually selling
like we meant it.